Su Zhang

Software Engineer

CONTACT ME

2 0451 991 558

suzhang79@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/su-zhang-au

https://github.com/coderGirlSu

https://codergirlsu.dev/

Sydney

EDUCATION

Certificate in Computer Science

Stanford Online

2023

Diploma of Information Technology

Coder Academy

2022

Bachelor of Architecture

Harbin Institute of Technology 2010 - 2013

SKILLS

- Full Stack Web App Development
- Backend Development
- Self Learning
- Problem solving
- · AWS fundamental services
- Mandarin native speaker

EXPERENCE

- Languages: JavaScript, Golang Node.js, TypeScript, Python, Ruby, HTML, CSS
- Frameworks: React.js, Vue.sj, Express, Ruby on Rails ,gRPC, Rest, Jest, Django, Django Rest Framework
- Software: VSCode, Figma, SourceTree, AutoCAD, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop
- Databases: PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Tools: Buildkite, Backstage, Kubernetes, Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Jira, Clickup, Trello, Heroku, Firebase, Agile Board, Postman, XMind, Balsamiq, draw.io

SUMMARY

I am a full-stack software engineer with one year of experience. I have a solid grasp of computer science and am a certified AWS Practitioner. I am passionate about building things and solving problems, especially using generative AI technologies such as LLMs.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Software Engineer Valearnis

Jan 2024 - Present

• Building an Al online learning platform using React, Typescript, Python, Django, Django Rest Framework and GPT-4.

Freelance Software Engineer Aetherworks

Dec 2023 - Present

• Automating a variety of manual business tasks on the e-commerce platform using Vue.js, JavaScript, PHP and Google APIs.

Full Stack Software Engineer Intern SafetyCulture

2022-2023

- Developed full-stack team projects in a microservice architecture that involved many different technologies, such as React, Typescript, Golang and Temporal workflow.
- Worked on a project to integrate the <u>Boston Dynamics Spot robot</u> image and temperature data sensors with the SafetyCulture application.

PROJECTS

Boston Dynamics Spot

- Created an innovative solution using the Boston Dynamics Spot robot that involved robotics programming to independently navigate a predetermined path, capturing high-quality photos and measuring temperature using infrared sensors.
- Utilised the data collected to conduct comprehensive inspections, integrating with the SafetyCulture platform to provide valuable insights into safety and maintenance requirements.
- Leveraged API development skills to upload media to devices used by SafetyCulture customers for more efficient and accurate inspections, enabling seamless access to valuable findings.

Temporal Workflow Engine

- Implemented Data Governance functionality, both frontend and backend, utilising technologies and tools, including Figma, React, TypeScript, gRPC, Go, and Temporal Workflow.
- Integrated Temporal Workflow to efficiently manage complex workflows.
- Presented the feature to a large audience of over 150 engineers and business stakeholders.
- Utilised in BAU to aid data migrations for both small and large customers.

AWS Cloud Practitioner Certificate

Credentials:

https://www.credly.com/badges/4519b7fc-ecbe-419c-8d2c-948bd3cafd34/public_url

- Proficient in core AWS cloud concepts, including cloud architecture, security, and billing, along with a deep understanding of fundamental AWS services and their use cases.
- Skilled in managing AWS cloud infrastructure, including virtual servers (EC2), storage (S3), and databases (RDS), ensuring optimal performance and cost-efficiency.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

OpenAI - Personal writing assistant tool

- Built a personal assistant tool using Golang that leverages AI technology from OpenAI's APIs and integrates into MacOS using Apple shortcuts.
- Features include translating text, enhancing writing, and grammar-checking using the GPT-4 model.
- **GitHub**: https://github.com/coderGirlSu/translate-tool

React - Fruit Picking Game

- Built a fruit-picking game using React, CSS, HTML and JavaScript.
- Includes features such as calculating the score, timer, and sound effects.
- App website: https://fruit.codergirlsu.dev/

MERN stack - Chat App

- Utilised the MERN stack framework to build a chat application that leverages React, Express, Node.js, MongoDB, Firebase, AWS EC2 and Netlify.
- Features include user authentication, group creation and chat rooms, chat history viewing, adding friends, dark mode, and a custom Halloween theme to enhance user experience.
- App website: https://tiktalk.codergirlsu.dev/
- GitHub: https://github.com/coderGirlSu/TikTalk-server

Hackathon - React Emoji Search App

- Built an app to search and copy emojis in a four-person team in one and a half days.
- Utilised React, JavaScript, CSS, and HTML, deployed on Netlify.
- Features include search and copy emojis, pop-up toast notifications, and dark mode.
- Collaboration with team using GitHub fork workflow and PRs.
- App website: https://emojis.codergirlsu.dev/
- YouTube presentation: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tTJmHlxH-fo
- GitHub: https://github.com/coderGirlSu/coder-academy-hackathon-team-why-not

RELATED EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Graphic designer 2019-2021

Access Displays & Digital Printing Pty Ltd

- Developed designs to meet client requirements using industry-standard design tools, including Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop.
- · Collaborated with a team of designers, clients and printing companies to create high-quality products and websites

Buildings Architect 2011-2018

Harbin University of Science and Technology

- Drew and designed architectural construction plans and architectural renderings that met client requirements and building regulations using AutoCAD, 3ds Max and SketchUp.
- Communicated with clients to determine planning project requirements and provide updates accordingly.
- Coordinated the design team to ensure aspects such as structural support, water, and electricity arrangements are coordinated throughout the project.

2023